世人沉睡的时候，恐惧，战兢，临到我身
《猛鬼街4：梦幻主宰》
- 你好 - 你住在这里吗
- Hello. - Do you live here?
这里没有人住
Nobody lives here.
- 佛莱迪在哪里 - 他不在家
- Where's Freddy? - Heh, heh. He's not home.
一 二 佛莱迪要来抓你了
One, two, Freddy's coming for you.
三 四 锁好你的门
Three, four, better lock your door.
五 六 快去拿十字架
Five, six, grab your crucifix.
冷静点 克莉丝丹
Be calm, Kristen.
乔伊 金凯德 救救我
Joey! Kincaid! Help me!
该死 克莉丝丹 又来了
Oh, shit, Kristen. Not again.
- 对不起 金凯德 - 对不起
- I'm sorry, Kincaid. - Sorry?
你是个可怕的女孩
You are one spooked chick.
乔伊
Joey.
- 谢天谢地 刚刚我还以为 - 什么
- Thank God. I thought for a minute…- What?
- 你把我们拖到这里来 - 对 别闹了
- Dragging us in here? - Yeah. Cut it out.
你严重影响到我睡美容觉
You're putting one serious dent in my beauty sleep.
是佛莱迪 他在这里 我听到他的声音了
It's Freddy. He's here. I heard him.
佛莱迪死了 他被火化埋葬 我们赢了 还记得吗
Freddy is dead, buried and consecrated. We won, remember?
- 他回来找我们 - 金凯德说的对
- He's coming back for us. - Kincaid's right.
佛莱迪·克鲁格已经成了过去 来吧
Fred Krueger's history. Come here.
这些水管是冷的 锅炉也是冷的 你自己看吧
The pipes are cold. The boiler is cold. See for yourself.
不知道
I don't know.
你好吗 强森先生
How are you, Mr. Johnson?
那条领带很漂亮
That's nice.
克莉丝丹 瑞克马上出来
Hi, Kristen. Rick will be out any second.
- 你要打扮成那样出门 - 这次又有什么问题
- You going out dressed like that? - What's wrong with it this time?
- 我到车边等 - 我也是
- I might just wait by the car. - Me too.
- 楼梯坏了吗 - 今天是全面避免接触日
- Something wrong with the stairs? - It's Avoid All Contact Day.
什么
What?
当爸拼命吃阿斯匹林时 就是全面避免接触日
When Dad's popping aspirin like popcorn, it's Avoid All Contact Day.
你们在等礼车吗
Waiting for a limo?
我要走了 亲爱的
I'm off to the club, honey.
我们走吧
Let's go.
好 这学期谁修三角函数
All right, anybody have trig this semester?
- 怎么回事 - 时间冲突 做功课还是看《朝代》
- What happened? - I had a conflict. Homework or Dynasty?
结果《朝代》赢了
And, uh, Dynasty won.
太可悲了 肥皂剧会要了你的命
Sad story. Soaps will kill you.
丹·乔登来了
Mm. There's Dan Jordan.
他可真是个大师哥
Mm. We are talking one major league hunk.
你真是个大师哥
You know, you are one major league hunk.
- 谢谢你 艾莉丝 - 地球呼叫艾莉丝
- Heh. Thanks, Alice. - Earth to Alice.
- 地球呼叫艾莉丝 你又恍神了 - 瑞克 拜托
- Earth to Alice. Hey, you spacing again? - Rick, please.
听我说 他是我的朋友 我可以帮你介绍
Well, tell you what, he's a friend of mine. I'll introduce you.
- 瑞克 - 开玩笑的 可是我会真的帮她介绍
- Rick. - Just kidding. But I would introduce her.
太棒了 我想我的救星来了
All right. I think I see salvation.
你怎么能骑这辆危害健康的车 难怪你会有气喘
How can you ride this health hazard? It's no wonder that you have asthma.
不 听着 气喘是遗传疾病
No, you see, asthma is an inherited condition.
偶尔看书能增进知识
Read a book now and then, you might know something.
说到看书 三角函数不是你的最爱吗
You know, speaking of books, isn't trig your favorite?
你又在看《朝代》了
Dynasty again?
小戴 帮大家一个忙 买部录影机
Deb, do us a favor and get a VCR.
宝贝 你吸错东西了
Hey, baby, you're sucking on the wrong nozzle.
听着 三寸钉
Hey, yo, needle dick.
我相信你是学校里唯一有生殖崇拜问题的男生
I bet you're the only male in this school suffering from penis envy.
我欠你一次
I owe you one.
- 真恶心 - 女超人 他已经死了
- So disgusting. - Hey, super girl, it's dead.
饶了那只虫子吧
Give a bug a break.
你们好
Hi, guys.
你们好 昨晚那样子 你只能这么说
Hi, guys? That's all you have to say after last night?
你们得小心一点 我是认真的 他回来了
You better be careful. I'm telling you, he's coming back.
听着 你有超能力 能把别人拉到你的梦里
Listen, you got this freak-o talent to bring folks into your dream…
但我们不需要了
…but we don't need it anymore.
我们该开始过正常生活
Time to start living like regular people.
对 忘了那一切 我是说
Yeah. Let it rest. I mean…
你有没有想过老是记得反而会把他引来
…did it ever occur to you that if you keep going in, you might stir him up again?
听着 我们可以帮你
Look, we'll help you.
我们有更美好的梦可以做
We all have better things to dream about.
你说的对 就那么说定
You got that right. Signed and sealed.
- 那这又是怎么一回事 - 那没什么意思
- Then what about this? - That don't mean dick.
我的狗跟我很像 把它拉进你的疯狂梦里 它会抓狂
My dog is like me. Drag him into your crazy dream, and he gets wild.
你男朋友来了 他能让你一夜好眠吗
Here comes your boyfriend. Can he give you a good night's sleep?
我们不会跟别人说自己的私事 你们呢
We don't kiss and tell. How about you?
- 听着 待会儿再谈 好吗 - 好的
- Look, we'll talk later, all right? - Okay.
那两个男生怪怪的
Those guys are kind of spooky.
- 那么你一定觉得我是怪胎 - 我一直无法下定决心
- Then you must think I'm a total freak. - I go back and forth.
放轻松 又没有人死掉
Hey, lighten up. No one died.
爸
Hi, Dad.
你在找东西吗
Looking for something?
猪头
Shithead.
我迟到了 我知道
I'm Iate. I know.
该死的合约
Damn contracts.
开动吧
Let's eat.
- 我们等了很久 - 所以我们不等了
- You know, we waited a long time. - And we gave up, as usual.
我今天工作了十小时 你让我吃青草
You call this vegetation a meal after a ten-hour workday?
我算什么 你当我是兔子吗
What the hell am l, a rabbit?
天啊 艾莉丝 多用点脑子
Christ, Alice, try to think a little more.
对 我会用脑子 想到我有多么厌倦
Yeah, I can think. I can think of how sick I am…
看着你酗酒然后把气发在我身上
…of watching you drink your life away and taking it out on me.
艾莉丝 我在跟你说话 你是清醒的吗
Alice, Alice, I'm talking to you. Are you awake or what?
- 爸 别说了 - 别说什么
- Dad, don't start. - Start what?
要爱做白日梦的人保持清醒
Telling the little daydreamer to wake up?
这也太久了
It's long overdue.
我不需要这样的挑衅
I don't need this aggravation.
杰森 快过来 真是只乖狗狗
Jason. Come on, boy. Come on. Come on. That's a boy.
你差点没吓死我
You almost scared me, boy.
快打开后车厢
Yo, open this sucker up!
该死
Damn.
这不是我的梦
This ain't my dreamland.
克莉丝丹
Kristen!
如果你在这里 我一定要痛扁你一顿
If you're here, I'm gonna pound your ass!
杰森
Jason.
Jason?
该死
Fucking A.
你们不该埋葬我 我没死
You shouldn't have buried me. I'm not dead.
太棒了
Yeah!
去死吧 王八蛋
Take that, motherfucker!
克莉丝丹 佛莱迪回来了
Kristen, Freddy's back!
佛莱迪回来了 佛莱迪回来了 佛莱迪回来了
Freddy's back! Freddy's back! Freddy's back!
地狱见了
I'll see you in hell.
跟他们说佛莱迪送你过去的
Tell them Freddy sent you.
解决一个 还有两个
One down, two to go.
MTV台 挑战理性
MTV in stereo defies the mind.
用音乐神游太空
Illusions of space through sound.
可能有泪水流下
There may be teardrops to shed.
我从寒冷中进来了
I'm coming in from the cold.
我每天早上起床后会看几小时的MTV台
I watch MTV every morning when I get up for a couple of hours.
早餐时会边吃边看
And then right around breakfast time, you know, I watch a little bit more.
午餐时我会喂鱼 边喂鱼边看MTV台
Then about lunch when I feed the fish, you know, I feed the fish and watch them…
等一下
Wait.
这是怎样一场春梦
How's this for a wet dream?
克莉丝丹 救救我
Kristen! Help!
- 乔伊 - 不
- Joey. - No!
大家好
Hi, guys.
这样反而没有用 对吧
Sort of defeats the purpose, don't it?
- 什么 - 镜子
- What? - The mirror.
你看不到镜子里的自己
You can't see yourself in it.
我不想照镜子
I don't want to.
如果妈还活着
You know, if Mom was still alive…
爸不会这样对我们
…Dad wouldn't treat us Iike this.
艾莉丝 你得学会为自己挺身而出
Alice, you gotta learn to stand up for yourself.
你知道的 反击
You know, fight back.
就像那样 一些皆由心生
Like that. It's all in the mind.
你会发现自己采取行动
You see yourself doing something.
身体自然地做出反应 譬如说
and your body reacts and does it. Like so:
- 就像那样 你来试试看 - 我吗 不 我不行
- Like that. Now you do it. - Me? No, I can't.
- 不 你可以的 - 不 我不行
- Yeah, yeah, you can. - No, I can't.
不 你可以的 站起来这么做
Yes, yes, yes, you can. Just get up there and just…
就像那样 用点力 来吧
Like that. Big and strong. Do it.
很好 艾莉丝 你得注意平衡
Good, good. But, Alice-san, you must have balance.
好了 来吧
Okay. So go to it.
太棒了 你杀死一只鱼
Swish. Killed a fish.
乔伊
Joey.
边吃边看
You know, I watch it for a little bit more.
午餐时我会喂鱼 边喂鱼边看MTV台
Then about lunch, when I feed the fish, you know, I feed the fish and watch…
乔伊 老是得帮你收脏衣服 我烦死了
Joey, I'm getting tired of picking up your clothes.
这个烂频道 该把电视关掉的
And this crap, I wish you'd turn it off.
乔伊
Joey.
原来你在这里
Here you are.
今天早上你跑到哪里去了 瑞克到处找你
Where were you this morning? Rick's looking all over.
你有看到乔伊跟金凯德吗 到处找不到他们
Have you seen Joey and Kincaid? I can't find them anywhere.
- 他们应该在学校里 - 嗯 我不确定
- I'm sure they're around. - Yeah, well, I'm not so sure.
我们得比看看谁的比较大
We have matching luggage again.
- 你的眼袋 做恶梦了吗 - 对
- The bags under your eyes. Nightmares? - Yeah.
天啊 我讨厌做梦
God, I hate dreaming.
我喜欢做梦 我只是讨厌梦到我爸
Mm, I love to dream. I just hate the ones about my Dad.
做恶梦时你会怎么办
How do you handle your nightmares?
小时候我妈妈教我一招
My Mom taught me when I was little.
你听过梦的主人吗
Did you ever hear of the dream master?
- 我觉得那像是益智节目主持人 - 不 那是首童谣
- Sounds like a game show host to me. - No, it's a rhyme.
你必须梦到一个有趣的地方 记住 一切由你控制
Just have to dream about someplace fun. Remember, you're in control.
你怎么会这么了解梦
How do you know so much about dreams?
如果你只剩下梦 当然会变成专家
Well, when it's all you have, you kind of become an expert.
我们快走吧 免得你哥组织搜索队来找我们
We better get going before your brother starts a search party.
总之我一直无法理解卡夫卡跟歌德
Anyway, Kafka and Goethe have never been irreconcilable to me.
克莉丝 你跑到哪里去了
Kris, where were you?
金凯德 乔伊 不会吧
Kincaid, Joey. No.
- 什么 - 他杀了他们
- Hey, what? - He killed them!
- 什么 等一下 冷静点 - 不
- What? Wait. Calm down. - No.
舒服一点了吗
Feeling better now?
舒服一点了
Yeah, I guess so.
发生了什么事
What happened?
你的头重重地撞了一下
You had quite a nasty bump.
- 我得离开这里 - 不 你得留下来
- I gotta get out of here! - No, no, no. You stay put.
你必须休息
You need your rest.
你不了解 他在追杀我
You don't get it. He's after me.
没事的 甜 ｡
It's okay, honey.
- 我得帮你抽点血 - 不
- I wanna draw some blood. - No!
不
No!
舒服一点了吗
Feeling better now?
发生了什么事
What happened?
你的头重重地撞了一下
You had quite a nasty bump.
我想成为你的骄傲和喜悦
I wanna be your pride and joy.
你会不会把我当成一个小玩具
Won't you treat me like a little toy.
你有看到瑞克吗
You seen Rick around?
- 没有 - 你是他妹妹 对吧
- No. - Well, you are his sister, right?
瑞克放学后还待在学校里 克莉丝丹不太舒服
Um, Rick stayed late after school. Kristen wasn't feeling very well.
你能跟他说我在找他吗
Could you tell him I'm looking for him?
对了 我是丹
Oh, by the way, I'm Dan.
对不起 艾莉丝 你下班了 我来服务他们
Sorry, Alice. Your shift's over. My table now.
大家好 丹 你好吗
Hi, guys. Hi, Dan. How you doing?
你好 我要可乐跟薯条
Hi. Um, can I get just a Coke and some fries?
你要听一下特餐内容还是要吃些甜点呢
Do you wanna hear our specials or do you want any dessert?
大师哥 要来点面包吗
Oh, hi, handsome. Care for some buns?
拿去吧 你在赶时间吗
Here. You in a hurry?
我得趁图书馆关门前赶过去 该死的物理学小考
I gotta get to the library before it closes. Killer physics test.
对啊 我根本没有时间念书
I know. I hardly have any time to study.
你不该在这里工作那么久
Maybe you shouldn't be working here so much.
你不会想一辈子当服务生吧
You don't wanna get stuck waiting tables the rest of your life.
我知道 那是我最大的恐惧
I know. It's my greatest fear.
他真的很帅
You know, he is so cute.
- 不知道他在哪里健身 - 省省力气吧 小戴
- I wonder where he works out? - Save it, Deb.
除了运动 还有别的生活
I mean, there is life after exercise.
总有一天 我会帮你介绍一个真正的男人
One of these days, I'm gonna set you up with a real guy…
让你知道你该做什么才对
…teach you to get your priorities straight.
我想席拉宁可解剖尸体
I think Sheila's more interested in dissecting bodies…
- 也不愿意看人们的外表 - 给她一点时间
- …than looking at the outside. - Give her time.
她的荷尔蒙总有一天会大爆发
Her hormones will kick in some day.
小戴 总有一天 你会了解我的座右铭
Deb, you know, later in life, you're gonna appreciate my motto.
- 什么座右铭 - 知性胜过物质
- What's that? - Mind over matter.
- 待会儿见 好吗 再见 - 再见
- Look, I'll see you later, okay? Bye. - Bye.
- 再见 艾莉丝 - 再见
- Bye, Alice. - Bye.
- 艾莉丝 你能下班了吗 - 怎么了
- Alice, can you leave here? - What's wrong?
昨晚金凯德跟乔伊都死了
Kincaid and Joey died last night.
- 什么 - 对
- What? - Yeah.
- 喂 瑞克 瑞克 - 对
- Hey, Rick. Rick! - Yeah.
陪着她
Stay with her.
克莉丝丹 发生了什么事
Kristen, what happened?
听着 你会听到各种说法
Look, you're gonna hear all kinds of stories.
我们一起经历了那么多事
And after all we've been through together…
我怎么能让他杀了他们
…how could I let him get to them?
我们曾是一个团队
We were a team.
- 我要逮到那个混蛋 - 谁
- I'm gonna get that son of a bitch. - Who?
瑞克 我们得走了
Rick, we gotta go.
- 快点 - 来了
- Now. - I'm coming.
- 我 马上回来 - 免得太迟
- I'll be right back. - Before it's too late.
- 我得走了 待会儿再谈 - 来吧
- I gotta go. I guess I'll talk to you later. - Come on.
为什么要到鬼屋来
So, uh, why the haunted house?
这不是一般的房子 这里是他家
It's not just a house. It's his home.
他在里面等着我做梦
And he's waiting in there for me to dream.
没事的 我们会陪着你
Hey, it's okay. We're with you.
我说过你是帮不了我的
I told you, you can't help me.
这不是一般的恶梦
This isn't a normal nightmare.
我死定了
I'm history.
我不了解
I don't get it.
- 来吧 - 我错过了什么
- Come on. - What'd I miss?
她跟我们提起佛莱迪的故事
She told us a story about Freddy.
佛莱迪·克鲁格 他是本镇的传奇人物
Fred Krueger. He's a town legend.
他是杀童凶手 不过因为程序问题获释
He was a child killer freed on a technicality.
- 所以呢 - 一些家长很不满
- So? - So a lot of parents got pissed off.
根据克莉丝的说法
And according to Kris…
他们抓住他 把他当成感恩节火鸡一样烧死
…they hunted him down and roasted him like a Thanksgiving turkey.
还不错的社区
Nice neighborhood.
对 总之怪的地方就在这里
Yeah. Anyway, that's where it gets weird.
她说他会在梦里回来
Um, she says that he comes back in dreams.
如果他在你的梦里杀了你 你是真的死了
And if he kills you in your dream, you're dead for real.
我要进入梦乡
Now I lay me down to sleep.
梦的主人 我要留住我的灵魂
The master of dreams, my soul I'll keep.
梦的主人 我就知道我记得那首童谣
Dream master, I think I remember the rhyme.
克莉丝丹 离那间房子远一点
Kristen, get the hell away from that house!
你不愿意的话 别离开 我会保护你的
Hey, hey, hey, you don't have to go if you don't want to. I'll take care of you.
- 我最好离开 - 好吧
- I better go. - Okay.
今晚我会打电话给你 我们会一起度过的
But I'll call you tonight, and we'll get through this.
- 好的 - 好的 再见
- Okay. - Okay. Bye.
再见
Bye.
艾莉丝
Alice.
坐驾驶位旁边
Shotgun.
菜不好吃吗
Something the matter with the cuisine?
妈 这么说吧
Well, Mom, I'll tell you.
如果你两个朋友在同一天死了
When two of your friends die in the same day…
告诉我你还能吃得下东西
…Iet me know what it does to your appetite.
你累了 别以为我没注意到你一直没睡
You're tired. Don't think I haven't noticed that you haven't been sleeping.
你不能再这样 甜心
That has got to stop, honey.
- 我是怎么了 - 青春期焦虑 你会好起来的
- What's wrong with me? - Adolescent anxiety. That'll make it better.
- 天啊 妈 你做了什么 - 天啊
- Oh, God. Mom, what did you do? - Oh, Christ!
天啊 安眠药
Jesus, sleeping pills?
- 听着 克莉丝丹 对不起 我 - 对不起
- Look, Kristen, I'm sorry. I'm just… - Sorry?
很抱歉你跟你的球友烧死这家伙 现在他要追杀我
Sorry that you and your tennis pals torched this guy, and now he's after me?
如果你一直没注意到
In case you haven't been keeping score…
他已经他妈的计划好了 我是他最后的目标
…it's his fucking banquet, and I'm the last course!
克莉丝丹 我们在心理医生那里谈过
Kristen, we went over this in therapy!
不 妈妈 你害死我了
No, mother. You just murdered me.
- 你跟你的心理治疗去死吧 - 克莉丝丹
- Take that to your goddamn therapy. - Kristen!
克莉丝丹
Kristen.
Kristen?
艾莉丝
Alice.
Alice. Alice.
梦到有趣的地方 梦到有趣的地方
Dream someplace fun. Dream someplace fun.
梦到
Dream some…
谢谢你 艾莉丝
Thanks, AIice.
你好 小妹妹
Hi, little girl.
你好
Hi.
- 你叫什么名字 - 艾莉丝
- What's your name? - Alice.
我朋友也叫艾莉丝
I have a friend named Alice.
不 不
No! No!
榆树街最后一个小鬼 再见
Elm Street's last brat. Farewell.
- 我们曾经打败过你 - 现在你只剩下一个人
- We beat you before! - And now you're all alone.
克莉丝丹 你何不
Kristen, why don't you, uh…
呼唤你的朋友 或许他们会帮你
…call on one of your little friends? Maybe they could help.
不行 我是最后一个
Never! I'm the last!
为什么你不找人帮忙
Why don't you reach out and touch someone?
不
No!
No! No!
不
No.
艾莉丝
Alice!
真可爱
How sweet!
新鲜货
Fresh meat.
艾莉丝 醒一醒 快逃走
Alice, wake up and get out!
艾莉丝 真的很抱歉 这是个错误
Alice, I'm so sorry. It was a mistake.
我拉你来这里
I pulled you in.
艾莉丝 到爸爸这里来
Alice, come to Daddy.
放了她 你这个混蛋
Leave her alone, you son of a bitch!
现在谁都不能睡觉
Now no one sleeps.
不
No!
我孩子们的灵魂
The souls of my children.
艾莉丝
Alice!
你会需要我的力量
You'll need my power.
- 你没事吧 - 克莉丝丹
- Are you okay? - Kristen.
克莉丝丹 我们得去她家
Kristen, we've gotta get to her house.
克莉丝丹
Kristen!
天啊 克莉丝丹 天啊
Oh, God! Kristen! Oh, God!
- 放开我 - 不 瑞克
- Let me go. - No. Rick.
艾莉丝 真希望你也来了
Hi, Alice. Wish you were here.
- 艾莉丝 - 你的讨厌哥哥又在玩老把戏
- Hi, Alice. - Your brother's up to his old tricks.
瑞克 自从认识你以来 我一直都想问你
Rick, as long as I've known you, I've always wanted to ask…
你到底在头发上抹了什么鬼东西
… what the hell this shit is that you put in your hair?
- 瑞克 跟我们谈谈你的性生活 - 不 不要
- Rick, tell us about your sex life. - Oh, no. Don't.
- 来吧 我很抱歉 - 不可以
- Come on. Sorry. - We can't.
- 来吧 - 不 你在做什么
- Come on. - No. What are you doing?
- 我说过我要他的身体 - 那是胡说八道
- I told you. I want his body. - Oh, that's bullshit.
- 你还要什么 - 她要我的身体
- What else do you want? - She wants my body.
克莉丝丹是我唯一的朋友
Kristen 's my only friend.
- 她是我唯一的朋友 - 对不起 我想要
- She 's my only friend. - Excuse me. I would like…
艾莉丝 你在做什么
Alice, what are you doing?
不知道
I don't know.
待会儿见 再见
See you later, bye.
来吧
Come on. Come on.
这能让我舒服一点
It makes me feel better.
用力 打中球 一定会没事的
Hit it. Hit the ball, everything will be great.
- 我一定会弄伤别人 - 用力
- I'm gonna hurt somebody. - Hit it.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
- 宝贝 - 太棒了
- Hello, baby. - Great.
当时你让她非常快乐
You made her so happy then.
对 直到佛莱迪出现
Yeah. Until all this Freddy shit.
- 为什么我没陪着她 - 结果还是会一样
- Why didn't I just stay with her? - lt wouldn't have made any difference.
一定会不一样的
Sure it would have.
不
No.
我在梦里都看到了
I saw it happen in my dream.
- 有个可怕的男人 - 谁 佛莱迪
- And there was this horrible man. - Oh, who? Freddy?
佛莱迪 我不想再听到佛莱迪的事 好吗
Freddy? I don't wanna hear about Freddy, okay?
我听到克莉丝丹满口都是这些事 我不想再听了
Heard it all from Kristen. I don't wanna hear any more.
我还可以闻到烟味
I could smell the smoke.
我还可以感觉到大火的热度
I could feel the heat from the fire.
- 那不是梦 - 别说了
- lt wasn't a dream! - Just stop it!
她没疯 你也没有 别说了 拜托
She wasn't crazy and neither are you, so just cut it out. Please.
天啊 你为什么要这么做
Jeez, why are you acting this way?
我不知道 瑞克
I don't know, Rick.
我觉得自己不一样了
I just feel so different.
梦里发生了一些事
Something happened in the dream.
现在一部分的她在我的身体里
And now it's like part of her is with me.
好吧
Okay.
- 克莉丝丹帕克小姐 天啊 - 我也爱你
- Miss Kristen Parker. Oh, my. - I love you too.
大家再见
Bye, everyone.
姊妹 我累死了
Phew, girl, I am so dead on my feet.
我们得比赛谁的眼袋比较大
We have matching luggage.
- 那是什么意思 - 昨晚你没睡吧
- What do you mean? - You didn't sleep last night?
那么明显啊
It's that obvious, huh?
那么你也看到他了
Then you saw him too.
看到谁了 我整晚没睡都在念物理
Saw who? I mean, I was up all night cramming for that physics test.
我还做了这个
Oh! And I put this little baby together.
你知道小戴多么怕虫子 我帮她做的
You know how Deb's afraid of bugs. Well, I made it for her.
超高频音波
Ultra-high soundwaves.
会把虫子吓走 吓到他们的触须掉下来
Make them run, screaming their antennas off.
课堂上见 好吗
Look, I'll see you in class, okay?
我不抽烟的
I don't smoke.
好 考试时间是四十分钟
All right, you've got 40 minutes.
（考试日）
祝大家好运 开始吧
So good luck and go for it.
艾莉丝 救救我 醒一醒 醒一醒
Alice. Help me. Help! Wake up! Wake up!
救命啊 救命啊
Help! Help!
醒一醒 该死
Wake up, damn it!
- 要亲一下吗 - 不要
- Wanna suck face? - No.
席拉 醒一醒
Sheila, wake up!
席拉
Sheila!
你被当掉了
You flunked.
席拉
Sheila.
席拉 快给她药
Sheila. Give her her thing.
你们没看到吗 他在这里了
Didn't you see it? He was here.
- 艾莉丝 你在胡说什么 - 他在这里了
- Alice, what are you talking about? - He was here!
拜托大家让一让
Out of the way, please.
- 请退后 别过来 - 退后
- Step back please. Stand back. - Step back.
气喘发作
Asthma attacked?
我来
I got it.
为什么17岁女孩会有致命气喘
What 17-year-old has fatal asthma?
天啊 她本来想当医生的
God, she was gonna be a doctor.
- 是佛莱迪干的 - 别胡说了
- lt was Freddy. - Enough with that crap.
我都看到了 说在我的梦里
I saw it. It was my dream.
我将席拉带到我的梦里
I brought Sheila in.
天啊
Oh, God.
我把席拉带到梦里 就像克莉丝丹把我带到梦里一样
I brought Sheila in like Kristen did with me.
不 不要 我把席拉送给他 现在她死了
No, don't. I gave Sheila to him. And now she's dead.
瑞克 我真的认为 克莉丝丹的故事开始影响到她
Hey, Rick, I really think Kristen's story is getting to her.
丹 我不认为那只是个故事
Dan, I really don't know if it's a story.
你看我们 我们一个个死了
Look at us. We're dropping off like flies here.
- 幸会 保重 再见 - 再见
- Good to see you. Take care. Bye. - Bye.
来吧
Come on.
我等不及要见你 你的图片不够
I can't wait to see you. Your picture ain't enough.
我等不及要碰你本人
I can't wait to touch you in the flesh.
对不起 小姐 能给我一包口香糖吗
Excuse me, miss. Can I get a pack of gum?
你跑到哪里去了 最近我一直没看到你
Hey. Where you been? I haven't seen you around lately.
我一直都在加班
I've been working double shifts.
看来你需要钱 对吧
Guess you need the extra money, huh?
说真的 你知道为什么 你只是不想相信我
Look, you know why. You just don't wanna believe me.
你不了解吗
Don't you understand?
我不能睡觉
I can't sleep.
可能会有人死掉
Someone might die.
遇见你女朋友 你是如此神圣
Met you with a girlfriend. You were so divine.
艾莉丝 假设这是真的
Alice, let's say that, uh, this is real, right?
为什么佛莱迪突然间要追杀你
Why, uh, all of a sudden is this Freddy guy after you?
杀害佛莱迪的那些人所生的孩子
Kristen was the last child left of.
最后一个活口说是克莉丝丹
the people who killed Freddy.
或许佛莱迪无法杀害新的孩子
Maybe Freddy can't get to the new kids…
除非有人将其他的孩子带到他面前
…unless there's someone to bring them to him.
丹尼 我们要来不及去露天电影院了
Danny, we're gonna be late for the drive in.
我得回去工作了
I have to get back.
待会儿见
Uh, I guess I'll see you later.
如果你说你好
'Cause if you say hello. It'll mean you wanna see me.
那意味着你本人要见我
in the flesh.
再过93天就放暑假了
Ninety-three days till summer vacation, man.
- 怎么了 你累了吗 - 不 我只是担心
- What's the matter, you tired? - No, I'm getting worried.
来看看我们能不能撑到暑假 这跟狩猎季节差不多
Let's see if we can make it until summer. It's like open season around here.
发生了很多怪事
Pretty weird stuff.
说到奇怪 你得同情那个家伙
Speaking of weird, you gotta feel for that guy.
女朋友死了 妹妹是个疯子
Dead girlfriend, basket case for a sister…
你何不学着闭嘴 混蛋
Why don't you learn to shut up, asshole?
- 天啊 真是个王八蛋 - 我知道
- God, what a dick. - I know.
- 你似乎很累 - 我一直在陪艾莉丝
- You look wasted, man. - I've been up with Alice.
她还好吧 昨晚我在餐厅里看到她
Hey, how's she doing? I, uh, saw her last night at the diner.
她因席拉的死自责
She's blaming herself for Sheila.
我能了解她的感觉 我一直都在想克莉丝丹
I know how she feels. I mean, I think about Kristen all the time.
我该相信她的 或许此能阻止这件事
You know, maybe I could have stopped it if I'd have listened.
- 你是指佛莱迪吗 - 不然呢
- You mean, uh, Freddy? - What else?
你查过本镇的历史吗 在这里当青少年真的很不安全
You ever take a look at our town's history? It's not a safe place to be a teenager.
孩子们 该走了 快点
Hey, bozos, let's hustle. Now.
如果我是下一个 你得小心点
Well, if I'm next, watch your back, man.
我们说到哪里了
Where were we?
每个古代社会
Every society dating back to the ancients…
都有关于梦的理论
…has had theories regarding dreams…
亚里斯多德 游荡的灵魂 也就是如何控制梦境
…what they mean, how to control them.
亚里斯多德相信人睡着后 灵魂会四处游荡
Aristotle believed that during sleep, your soul roams free.
灵魂看到的事说是梦境
What it sees are dreams.
有技巧的做梦者 可以控制自己看到的一切
The skilled dreamers, well, they are able to control what they see.
有个神话指出 灵魂可以进入两扇大门
There is a myth that there's two gates your soul can enter.
一是正面的大门
One is a positive gate…
还有负面的大门
…the other, a negative gate.
关键是有个梦的主人
The key element is that there's a dream master…
他守护着正面的大门 事实上他是在保护睡着的主人
…someone who guards the positive gate and, in fact, protects the sleeping host.
整体来说 这些说法提供了
Taken altogether, they offer a fascinating perspective…
非常迷人的古老历史观
…on ancient history.
不觉得有趣的人
Now those of you who don't find it fascinating…
最好注意听着 因为期末考会考这个
…you better listen up, because it's gonna be on the final.
瑞克 逗我笑
Rick, make me laugh.
电梯向下
Going down.
什么
What?
真正的战士不需要眼睛
A true warrior needs no eyes.
快出来跟我打 你这个胆小鬼
Come on out and fight me, you chickenshit.
忍者战士必须冷静
Ninja warriors have calm.
找到你的平衡 瑞克
Find your balance, Rick.
你胆小到不敢现身吗 克鲁格
Too wimpy to show yourself, Krueger?
这样的平衡可以吗
Well, how's this for balance?
对
Yes.
你没有武器 要怎么跟我打 佛莱迪
How you gonna fight me without your weapon, Freddy?
再见 瑞克
Sayonara, Rick-san!
不
No!
我虽然走过死荫的幽谷 也不怕遭害
…through the valley of the shadow of death, I shall fear no evil…
因为你与我同在 你的杖 你的竿
…for thou art with me with thy rod and thy staff…
各位 今天我们来到这里 哀悼瑞克·强森之死
Dearly bereaved, we gather here in remorse for Rick Johnson.
这个年轻人的死让我们感到悲伤 也百思不得其解
A young man whose death confounds and mystifies us…
瑞克正值青春 大家都爱他
…for Rick was in his prime, beloved by all…
代表着年轻人的理想
…exemplary of young men's ideals…
跟坚强的道德观
…and of strong moral fiber.
我们为我们的损失感到悲伤
We grieve our loss,
也很安慰我们知道这样的一个人
but take comfort in knowing such a man…
会在上帝的国度里安息
…rests in the kingdom of God.
让我们用信念取代知识
Let our faith supersede our knowledge…
因为上帝的作为自有其道理
…for truly the Lord works in mysterious ways.
嗨 宝贝
Hello, baby.
我爱死这一切了
I Iove this.
他们以为我死了 对吧
They think I'm dead, don't they?
这真的太棒了
This is great.
干嘛哭呢
Hey. What's with the tears?
我不会离开你的 来吧 别哭了
I wouldn't leave you. Come on, don't cry.
我在这里 这是开玩笑了 为了骗佛莱迪开的玩笑
I'm here. It was a joke. A big joke to fool Freddy.
来吧 笑一个给我看
Come on, smile for me.
我不做白日梦了
No more daydreams.
我得走了
Well, gotta go.
晚安
Good night.
艾莉丝 你没事吧
Alice. You okay?
我一点都不好
Not really.
有什么是我们能帮忙的吗
Is there anything we can do?
我想应该没有
I don't think so.
这是我一个人的战争
I guess this is my own war.
不 不是的
No. No, it's not.
我们都得活下去
We all have to survive.
听着 我花那么多时间运动
I mean, look, I don't spend hours working out…
才不会让一个黑夜跟踪狂打败我
…to let some night stalker beat me.
你真的不了解
You don't really get it.
他不是黑夜跟踪狂
He's not a night stalker.
光做卧推是无法打败他的
And it'll take more than bench presses to beat him.
- 我们该怎么办 - 今晚到戴比家碰面
- So, what do we do? - Let's go over to Debbie's tonight.
- 我们得计划一下 - 艾莉丝
- We have to make a plan. - Alice!
我得走了
I gotta go.
- 八点我到餐厅接你好吗 - 好的
- How about I pick you up at the diner at 8? - Uh, yeah.
拿去吧 这是幸运手环
Here. It's a good luck charm.
可以为你害怕的那个混蛋带来恶运
Brings bad luck to the creep you flatten with it.
就是这个
This is it.
知性胜过物质
Mind over matter.
Mind over matter?
以前席拉常那么说
Sheila used to say that.
天啊 她每天都变得不一样
God, every day, she changes.
不
No.
每次有人死了 她都变得不一样
It's after every death.
我是怎么回事
What's happening to me?
艾莉丝 你要去哪里
Alice, where are you going?
我要去找戴比
Just to see Debbie.
不 你不能出门
No, you're not.
我要你待在家里
I want you to stay in.
爸 我非去不可 你是阻止不了我的
Dad, I gotta go, and there's nothing you can do about it.
艾莉丝
Alice.
- 不 - 你无权阻止我
- No. - You have no right to stop me.
如果你知道会发生什么事
If you just knew what was going on…
我知道你跟你的朋友们 发生了什么事
I know very much what's going on with you and your friends.
对 大家都以为他们知道 但他们根本不了解
Yeah. Everybody thinks they know, but they don't.
看着我 艾莉丝
Look at me, AIice.
我失去瑞克 因为我没有看好他
I Iost Rick because I didn't watch him.
我不要失去你
I don't wanna lose you.
我们只剩下彼此了
We're all we have.
在美国有那么多小镇
All the towns in America…
我却搬到百慕达三角洲
…and I gotta move to the Bermuda Triangle.
真的太棒了
That's great.
把你的手放在我身上
I want your hands on me.
丹
Dan?
（丽多电影院 迷失的燃烧年轻人）
（大麻疯潮）
- 不 - 吉米
- Oh, no. - Jimmy. Jimmy.
原来你在这里 女士
There you are, ma'am.
他不是送报生
Hey, he ain't no paperman.
什么 你不认识他 他是曲指师哥
Why, don't you know him? That's Hot Fingers Curly.
天啊 他真的很会跳舞
Boy, he really swings out hopping with a jive.
- 你要跳舞吗 - 当然要
- Do you want to dance? - Do I?
不
No!
你要点什么
What will it be?
快告诉我 甜心 我不想一辈子待在这里
Come on, honey. I don't wanna be here forever.
就算食物没要了你的命 你也会被这里的服务气死
If the food don't kill you, the service will.
救救我们 艾莉丝
Help us, Alice!
- 我喜欢的口味 - 不
- Mm! The usual. - No!
不 艾莉丝 别让他那么做
No, Alice, don't let him do it!
我的最爱
My favorite.
- 不 快点 - 点 点 点
- No! Come on, no! - Eeney, meeney, miney…
- 快点 不 - 莫
- Come on, no! - …moe.
不 艾莉丝 别让他那么做
No, Alice, don't let him do it!
瑞克 你这个小肉丸子
Rick, you little meatball.
- 我喜欢灵魂食物 - 不
- I love soul food. - No, no.
住手
Stop!
多帮我带些孩子过来
Bring me more.
你可以下班了
Your shift is over.
我想要你来请我
I want you to come and please me.
把你的手 放在我身上
Put 'em on, put 'em on, put 'em on me Put 'em on, put 'em on, put 'em on me.
来吧 我们得快一点
Come on. We have to hurry.
- 发生了什么事 - 我开车
- What's going on? - I'm driving.
他的目标是戴比 我得阻止他
He's going after Debbie. I gotta stop him.
我们得阻止他 这件事我会帮你的
We gotta stop him. I'm with you on this thing.
我要帮你 我站在你这边 好吗
I wanna help you. I'm on your side, okay?
我要你爱我 碰我
I want you to love me. And just touch me.
把你的手 把你的手放在我身上
Put your hands. Put your hands on me.
把你的手放在我身上 把你的手放在我身上
Put your hands on me. Put your hands on me.
把你的手 放在我身上
Put 'em on, put 'em on, put 'em on me Put 'em on, put 'em on, put 'em on me.
我们到了
Here we are.
来吧 我们得快一点
Come on. We have to hurry.
- 发生了什么事 - 我开车
- What's going on? - I'm driving.
把你的手 放在我身上
Put 'em on, put 'em on, put 'em on me.
- 我不相信你是真的 - 我相信你是真的
- I don't believe in you. - I believe in you.
没有付出
No pain…
怎么会有收获
…no gain.
他的目标是戴比 我得阻止他
He's going after Debbie. I gotta stop him.
救命啊
Help me!
到了
Here we are.
来吧 我们得快一点
Come on. We have to hurry.
- 发生了什么事 - 我开车
- What's going on? - I'm driving.
他的目标是戴比 我得阻止他
He's going after Debbie. I gotta stop him.
我觉得怪怪的 我们好像这样做过
You know, I got the weirdest feeling we've done this before.
来吧 我们得快一点 我开车
Come on. We have to hurry. I'm driving.
我们得快一点 我开车
We have to hurry. I'm driving.
天啊 我们两个都睡着了
Oh, my God. We're both asleep.
他让我们鬼打墙
He's got us going in circles.
我们得快一点
We gotta go!
你可以进来 但你出不去的
You can check in, but you can't check out.
那到底是怎么一回事
What the hell was that?
戴比 她死了
Debbie. She's gone.
我把她带入梦里 就跟其他孩子一样
I've collected her, Iike the others.
好吧 我要撞死他
All right, I'm gonna punch his ticket in.
丹
Oh, Dan.
对不起
I'm sorry.
好吧 快送他上车
Get him in there.
基地 这是七号救护车
Base, this is med seven.
伤者是白人男性 16至18岁
We have a male Caucasian, approximately 16 to 18 years of age.
头部跟颈部有多处撕裂伤
Uh, multiple lacerations about the head and neck area.
可能有内伤
Possible internal injuries.
- 那是什么 - 能让你的男朋友放松
- What's that do? - Relaxes your boyfriend.
- 放下针筒 - 抱歉 规定就是规定
- Put the needle down. - Sorry, rules is rules.
他得保持清醒
He stays awake!
那是我的规定 懂吗
Those are my rules, understand?
怎么了 你疯了吗
What are you, nuts?
他会过敏 好吗
He's allergic, okay?
你一开始就该跟我说的
You should have said something in the first place.
该死的小鬼
Damn kids.
别让他们为你注射镇定剂
Don't Iet them put you to sleep.
- 我们得为他准备好 - 好的
- We have to get ready for him. - Okay.
夏克医生请立刻到手术室
Dr.Schick to OR, stat.
- 他什么时候动手术 - 15分钟后
- When does he have surgery? - Fifteen minutes.
让他去吧 艾莉丝
Let him be, Alice.
- 他们会杀了他 - 你在胡说什么
- They're gonna kill him. - What are you talking about?
- 放开我 - 艾莉丝
- Let me go. - Alice.
该死 快回来 艾莉丝
Damn it. Get back here! Alice!
艾莉丝
Alice!
快点
Come on!
- 不 - 我不要麻醉
- No. - No gas.
我不要麻醉 不 不要
No gas. No. Don't put…
该死
Fucking A.
- 克鲁格 - 我可不是苏斯博士
- Krueger. - Well, it ain't Dr.Seuss.
艾莉丝
Alice! Alice!
艾莉丝 艾莉丝
离他远一点 你这个混蛋
Get away from him, you son of a bitch!
- 丹 - 我看到他了 他刚刚在这里
- Dan. - I saw him. He was here.
我知道 我们得离闭这个地方
I know. We have to get out of this place.
丹
Dan.
要逛逛吗 小情人们
Out for a spin, lovebirds?
丹 抓紧了
Dan, hold on.
艾莉丝 艾莉丝
Alice! Alice!
艾莉丝 太迟了
Alice, it's too late.
他在大出血 让他醒过来 快点
He's hemorrhaging. Bring him out of it. Hurry!
艾莉丝
Alice.
艾莉丝 艾莉丝
Alice! Alice!
你们得立刻麻醉我
You gotta put me back under now.
放轻松 孩子 我们好不容易让你醒来
Relax, son. It was rough, but we pulled you out.
你会没事的
You're gonna be okay.
佛莱迪要来抓你了
Freddy's coming for you.
三 四 锁好你的门
Three, four, better lock your door.
五 六 快去拿十字架
Five, six, grab your crucifix.
七 八
Seven, eight…
欢迎来到仙境 艾莉丝
Welcome to Wonderland, Alice.
你有他们的能力 我有他们的灵魂
You've got their power. I've got their souls.
来吧
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
你以为你真的能办到吗
You think you've got what it takes?
我守着我的大门 已经非常久了 臭女孩
I've been guarding my gate for a long time, bitch.
我是永恒
I am eternal.
让我睡着
Now I lay me down to sleep.
梦的主人会拿走我的灵魂
The master of dreams. My soul, I'll keep.
在我心灵之眼的倒影里
In the reflection of my mind's eye…
邪恶会看到自己 它将会死去
Evil will see itself, and it shall die.
放了他们
Let them out!
你死定了 克鲁格
You're dead, Krueger.
谢谢你 艾莉丝
Thank you, Alice.
你救了我们 艾莉丝
You saved us, Alice.
- 再见 - 再见
- Goodbye. - Bye.
下地狱去吧
Rest in hell.
昨晚我睡了一整夜 我好几天没有睡得那么好了
You know, I slept through all of last night and I haven't done that in days.
我还是睡不好
I'm still having trouble.
我可以睡上两小时 运气好的话是三小时
I can sleep two, maybe three hours if I'm lucky.
但我不介意
I don't mind though.
现在我有理由让自己保持清醒
I have more reasons to stay awake now.
来吧
Come on.
许个愿
Make a wish.
少来了 你竟会相信那种事
Oh, come on, you don't believe in that stuff.
对 我相信 我想你也相信
Uh, yeah, I do, and I think you do too.
来吧
Here it goes.
你许了什么愿
What'd you wish for?
说出来的话就不会成真了
If I tell you, it won't come true.